needhits.net 2008-12-18

# OUR TERMS

**Your personal privacy is very important to Needhits.net**. To better protect your privacy, we provide this privacy policy notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. To make this privacy policy notice easy to find, we make it available in our Web site at every point where personally identifiable information will be requested.

(Back To Top)

**This privacy policy notice applies to all information collected in the Needhits.net Web site**. On some pages, you can order services or make requests. The types of personal information collected in these by paypal.com our payment processor are: name, address, email address, credit card information, and etc.  We do not collect, nor retain, any personal financial information on our website pages.

We DO NOT collect any personal information from our site visitors and/or Web site clients by way of cookies or beacons, (non-identifying and aggregate information). We DO NOT permit any entity to contact or retrieve personal information from our site visitors.  Your personal privacy is very important to Needhits.net.

(Back To Top)

**Personally identifiable information collected by Needhits.net will ONLY be used** strictly for the purpose of setting up your traffic campaign(s), its service and administration. We will use the information you provide about yourself when placing an order or request, only to complete that order or request. We do not share this information with outside parties. We use return email addresses to answer emails we receive. Such email addresses are not used for any other purpose and are not shared with outside parties. In rare occasions, we may also disclose personally identifiable information in a response to a court order, or at other times, when we believe we are reasonably required to do so by law.

(Back To Top)

To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, maintain e-commerce security, and to ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure any personal information we collect online. All information transmitted to Needhits.net remains the property of Needhits.net International and will not be released to third parties. Be advised, that any information submitted to Needhits.net is transmitted through a highly secure server using the latest SSL encryption technology.

(Back To Top)

Protecting the privacy of children is especially important to Needhits.net. For that reason, we never collect or maintain personal information at our Web site from those that are under the age of 13. No part of this Web site is structured or designed to attract anyone under the age of 18.

(Back To Top)

Personally identifiable information that we collect online and maintain can be changed by [contacting Needhits.net](http://needhits.net/support.php). We use this procedure to better safeguard your filed personal information. You can correct factual errors pertaining to your personally identifiable information by sending us a request that credibly reflects the error(s). To protect the online privacy of consumers, we will also take reasonable steps to verify your identity before making corrections.

(Back To Top)

Should you have other questions or concerns about this privacy policy notice, please call us at (614)-491-3486 or send us an email on our **[Contact Form](http://needhits.net/support.php)**. If you are an online consumer and you feel your online privacy or security rights have been violated, please [file a complaint](http://needhits.net/support.php).

(Back To Top)
